Finding Aid for the Dewey Daane Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 6, 11/14/84 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 7, 11/28/84 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 8, 12/5/84 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 9, 12/12/84 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Final exam, 12/18/84 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Fall, 1983 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture #1, 9/7/83 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture #1a 9/21/83 Maneschi (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Mid semester exam, 10/12/83 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 2, 10/19/83 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 3, 10/26/83 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 4, 11/2/83 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 5, 11/9/83 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 6, 11/16/83 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 7, 11/23/83 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 8, 11/30/83 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 9, 12/7/83 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Bob Solomon OSSA, 12/2/83 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Final exam, 12/14/83 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Fall, 1982 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 1, 10/13/82 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Mid Semester exam, 10/20/82 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 2, 10/20/82 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 3, 10/27/82 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 4, 11/3/82 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 5, 11/10/82 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 6, 11/17/82 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 7, 11/24/82 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 8, 12/1/82 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 8a, 12/1/82 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 9, 12/8/82 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Fall, 1981 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 1 With Maneschi, 9/9/81 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Mid Semester exam, 10/28/81 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 2, 10/7/81 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 3, 10/14/81 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 4, 10/21/81 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 5, 11/4/81 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 6, 11/11/81 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 7, 11/18/81 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 8, 11/25/81 (Box 70)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 9, 12/2/81 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 9a 12/2/81 Eurodollars (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 9b 12/2/81 Intl. Banking Regulations (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 10, 12/9/81 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Final Exam, 12/18/81 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Course #436 Fall, 1980 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture #1, 9/3/80 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – 10/8/80 Coles (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 2, 10/15/80 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 3, 10/22/80 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 3a 10/22/80 Balance of Payments (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 4, 10/29/80 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 5, 11/5/80 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 6, 11/12/80 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 7, 11/19/80 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 8, 11/26/80 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 9, 12/3/80 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 8a 11/26/80 Eurodollars (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Final Exam Part 1, 11/24/80 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Final Exam Part 2, 12/13/80 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Course 532 Fall 1979 Coles and Daane (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 1, 9/12/79 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 2, 9/26/79 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 3, 10/10/79 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 4, 11/7/79 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 5 11/21/79 Mid term exam (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture #6a, 11/28/79 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 6b, 11/28/79 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 6c, 11/28/79 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 7, 12/5/79 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 7a, 12/5/79 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Fall 1978 Coles and Daane (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture #1, 9/6/78 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 2a, 10/11/78 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 2b, 11/1/78 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 3, 11/8/78 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 4a, 11/15/78 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture #4b, 11/15/78 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture #5, 11/22/78 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 6, 11/29/78 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 7, 12/6/78 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 7a, 12/6/78 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 7b, 12/6/78 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 7c, 12/6/78 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Course 532 Fall, 1977 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Coles Lecture on Balance of Payments and Mid Term exam, 10/12/77 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture #1, 10/19/77 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 2, 10/24/77 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 3, 10/31/77 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 4, 11/2/77 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 5, 11/7/77 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 6, 11/9/77 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 7, 11/14/77 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 8, 11/16/77 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 9, 11/21/77 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 10, 11/23/77 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 12, 11/30/77 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Gretchen Greene Guest Lecture, 11/30/77 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 13, 12/5/77 (Box 71)
- International Finance and Economics – Lecture # 14, 12/7/77 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Fall, 1976 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 1, 10/25/76 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 2, 10/27/76 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 3, 11/1/76 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 4, 11/3/76 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 5, 11/8/76 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 6, 11/10/76 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture #7, 11/15/76 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 8, 11/17/76 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 9, 11/22/76 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 10, 11/24/76 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 11, 11/29/76 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 12, 12/1/76 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 13, 12/6/76 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 14, 12/8/76 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Oct 1975 Class Register Outline (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 1, 10/27/75 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture #2, 10/29/75 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture #3, 11/3/75 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 4, 11/5/75 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 5 and 6, 11/10/75 and 11/12/75 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 7, 11/17/75 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 8, 11/19/75 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 9, 11/24/75 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 10, 11/26/75 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 11, 12/1/75 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture #12, 12/3/75 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 13, 12/8/75 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture #14, 12/10/75 (Box 71)
- Vanderbilt Course in International Finance (Box 71)
- Class Outlines (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 1, 10/28/74 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 2, 10/30/74 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 3, 11/4/74 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture #4, 11/6/74 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 5, 11/11/74 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 6, 11/14/74 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 7, 11/18/74 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 8, 11/20/74 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 9, 11/25/74 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 10 and #11, 11/27/74 and 12/2/74 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture #12, 12/4/74 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 13, 12/9/74 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 14, 12/11/74 (Box 71)
- International Finance – Lecture # 15, 12/16/74 (Box 71)
- Capital Adequacy (Box 72)
- Federal Funds (Box 72)
- GAO Audit, 1973-1974 (Box 72)
- Testimony (Box 72)
  - Testimony (Box 72)
  - Briefing Book for Chairman Burns Testimony, 9/15/72 (Box 72)
- Financial Structure and Regulation, Presidents Commission (Hunt Commission) (Box 72)
- President’s Commission on Financial Structure (Box 72)
- Analysis of Hunt Commission Report (Box 72)
  - -Loose Materials (Box 72)
  - -Now Accounts (Box 72)
  - -Monetary Policy (Box 72)
- Housing Study (Box 72)
- Bernstein Reports (Box 72)
- Golembe Reports (Box 72)
- Loose Materials- Three reports from Congressional meetings on the Modification of the Par Value of the Dollar, Feb/Mar 1972 (Box 72)
- Large Binder- Senate and House Committee Hearings on the Par Value Modification Act, Feb-Mar 1972 (Box 73)
- Expandable File- G-10 Smithsonian Meeting Dec 1971 Eurodollar, June 1969 (Box 73)
- The Eurodollar-Original, 1964 (Box 73)
- FRB Richmond- Federal Observer, 1958-1960 (Box 73)
- FRB Richmond- Federal Observer, 1956-1957 (Box 73)
- FRB Richmond- Federal Observer, 1954-1955 (Box 73)
- FRB Richmond- Federal Observer, 1952-1953 (Box 73)
- FRB Richmond- Federal Observer Vol. IV and Vol. V (Box 73)
- FRB Richmond- Federal Observer Vol. I, Vol. II and Vol. III (Box 73)
- International Finance and Economic Reference Materials, 1986 (Box 74)
- International Financial; Conference Seoul, Korea, 10/7/85 (Box 74)
- J.D.D.’s Clippings from Seoul- Japan (Box 74)
- International Clippings, 1985 (Box 74)
- International Finance and Economics Reference Materials Fall 1985 International Clippings, 1984 (Box 74)
- International Clippings, 1984 (Box 74)
- Staff Studies Pamphlets for FRB Governors (Box 74)
- 40th Anniversary Breton Woods Monetary Conference, May 1984 (Box 74)
- Papers from Breton Woods Monetary Conference, 1984 (Box 74)
- Federal Reserve Bank of Boston 40 yrs. After Breton Woods 5/18/84-/5/20/84 (Box 74)
- Materials from FRB of Boston 40 yrs. After Breton Woods (Box 74)
- International Finance and Economics Reference Materials Fall, 1984 (Box 74)
- No Label- International Finance and Economics Reference Materials, 1983 (Box 74)
- International Finance and Economics #3, 10/27/82 (Box 74)
- International Finance and Economics Reference Materials Fall, 1982 (Box 74)
- - Washington Group of 10 Meeting, Sept 24, 1972 (Box 75)
- G-10 Meeting Jun 13, 1972 Paris, France (Box 75)
- Briefing Materials G-10 Deputies Meeting June 13, 1972 Paris (Box 75)
- - Montreal Meeting of G-10 Deputies, May 11, 1972 (Box 75)
- - 12:30pm London Meeting of Selected G-10 Deputies Reactions to G-10 Washington Meeting 12/17/71-12/18/71 Cables, April 23, 1972 (Box 75)
- - Paris Working Party 3 Meeting, Oct 18, 1971 (Box 75)
- G-10 Deputies Meeting Dec 16, 1971 Washington DC (Box 75)
- G-10 Ministers Meeting Nov 30-Dec 1, 1971 Rome, Italy (Box 75)
- G-10 Ministers and Deputies meeting Misc. Nov 27- Dec 2, 1971 Rome, Italy (Box 75)
- G-10 Ministers and Deputies Meeting Misc. Nov 27- Dec 2, 1971 Rome, Italy (Box 75)
- Volcker Groups Reference Materials for G-10 Mtg., Nov 27- Dec 2, 1971 (Box 75)
- Nov 29, 1971 Rome: Deputies Meeting- G-10, Nov 27- Dec 2, 1971 (Box 75)
- G-10 Ministers and Deputies Meeting Sept 25-26, 1971 Washington DC (Box 75)
- Briefing Materials G-10 Deputies WP3 Oct 18-20, 1971 Paris (Box 75)
- Nov 30-Dec 1, 1971 Rome: Ministers and Deputies Meeting G-10 (Box 75)
- Volcker Group Meeting Principals Only, Oct 11, 1971 (Box 75)
- Misc. File- Paris, Oct 1971 (Box 75)
- G-10 and WP-3 Meeting Material; Misc., 10/15/71 (Box 75)
- Rate Realignment (Box 75)
- Paris G-10 Deputies Meeting, Oct 19, 1971 (Box 75)
- G-10 Ministers and Deputies Meeting Nov 30-Dec 1, 1971 Rome, Italy (Box 75)
- Volcker Group Meeting Sept 22, 1971 Principals only (Box 75)
- Cable and other Reports on G-10 Meeting London England, Sept 1971 (Box 75)
- Statements by Ministers and Governors at G-10 Meeting London England, Sept 1971 (Box 75)
- G-10 Ministerial Meeting (Misc.), Sept 15-16, 1971 (Box 75)
- Bilateral Briefing Material G-10 Ministers and Governors Sept 15-16, 1971 London (Box 75)
- G-10 Ministerial Meeting Sept 15-16, 1971 London England (Box 75)
- G-10 Deputies Meeting Sept 3-4, 1971 Paris France (Box 75)
- G-10 Deputies Meeting Paris- Rome Trip with Mr. Volcker Sept 2-5 1971 Misc. Folder (Box 75)
- Memorandum of Conversation Mario Ferrari Aggradi et al Rome Italy, Sep 5, 1971 (Box 76)
- VG Documents, (Aug-Sept 1971) (Box 76)
- Volcker, Daane, and Dale Meeting at IMF with Exec. Directors re Less Developed Countries, Sept 8, 1971 (Box 76)
- Memorandum of Conversation Dr. J. Zijlstra – Paris France, Sept 4, 1971 (Box 76)
- Briefing Material G-10 Ministers and Governors Sept 15-16, 1971 London (Box 76)
- Contingency Planning-, August 1971 (Box 76)
- Briefing Material G-10 Deputies Sept 3-4, 1971 Paris (Box 76)
- Governor Daane- A (Box 76)
- Governor Daane- B (Box 76)
- Governor Daane- C (Box 76)
- Governor Daane- D (Box 76)
- Governor Daane- E (Box 76)
- Meeting in Bonn, Germany Nov 21, 22, and 23, 1968 (Box 76)
- Balance of Payments (Box 76)
- Special CBOT Committee Meeting, Dec 1, 1981 (Box 76)
- Special CBOT Committee Meeting, Dec 7, 1981 (Box 76)
- Chicago Broad of Trade Directors Meeting, Nov 17, 1981 (Box 76)
- Special CBOT Committee Meeting, Dec 1, 1981 (Box 76)
- Special CBOT Committee Meeting, Nov 24, 1981 (Box 76)
- CBO Panel of Economic Advisors (Box 76)
- Evaluation of CBO (Box 76)
- Congressional Budget Office (CBO) Washington DC, June 9, 1987 (Box 76)
- Congressional Budget Office Thursday, Dec 11, 1986 (Box 76)
- Congressional Budget Office Panel of Economic Advisors, 12/10/85 (Box 76)
- Congressional Budget Office Panel of Economic Advisors Meeting, 6/24/85 (Box 76)
- Congressional Budget Office Economic Advisors Meeting, 12/11/84 (Box 76)
- DC Congressional Budget Office Panel of Economic Advisors Meeting, June 20, 1984 (Box 76)
- Congressional Budget Office Panel of Economic Advisors Meeting, 12/7/83 (Box 76)
- Congressional Budget Office Washington DC, Sept 14, 1983 (Box 76)
- Congressional Budget Office, July 1983 (Box 76)
- Congressional Budget Office Meeting, 12/20/82 (Box 76)
- Congressional Budget Office Meeting, 7/9/82 (Box 76)
- Congressional Budget Office Meeting, 12/16/81 (Box 76)
- Congressional Budget Office Meeting, 7/9/81 (Box 76)
- Congressional Budget Office Meeting, 2/2/81 (Box 76)
- Congressional Budget Office Meeting, 6/17/81 (Box 76)
- Congressional Budget Office Panel of Economic Advisors Meeting, 1/7/80 (Box 76)
- Congressional Budget Office, 6/4/79 (Box 77)
- NABE Annual Forecasting Conference, 12/7/82 (Box 77)
- NABE 24th Annual Meeting 9/21-24/82 Economic Retrospects and Prospects (Box 77)
- NABE Fall Review, 1981 (Box 77)
- NABE Meeting Crystal City Marriott, Arlington VA, 3/19/81 (Box 77)
- NABE Meeting Washington DC, 1/22/80 (Box 77)
- NABE Meeting, 1/22/80 (Box 77)
- NABE Study-Meeting, 2/6/79 (Box 77)
- NABE Study (Box 77)
- Gertrude Manley Fellowship (Box 77)
- Harvard Graduate Society 350th Anniversary, 9/4-7/86 (Box 77)
- Harvard 350th Anniversary Celebration, 9/4-7/86 (Box 77)
- Kennedy School of Government Executive Council (Box 77)
- KSG Alumni Assn. Executive Council Meeting Harvard U., 11/5-6/82 (Box 77)
- KSG Alumni Assn. Executive Council Cambridge, Mass, 10/16-17/81 (Box 77)
- KSG Alumni Day and Executive Council Meeting, 10/17-18/80 (Box 77)
- KSG Alumni Day, 3/8/80 (Box 77)
- Harvard Executive Committee Meeting Cambridge, Mass, 11/2/79 (Box 78)
- KSG Executive Council Meeting Washington DC, 6/2/79 (Box 78)
- KSG Alumni Day, 3/9-10/79 (Box 78)
- KSG Dedication Ceremony, 10/21/78 (Box 78)
- Executive Council Meeting KSG Assn. 9/17/77 Bethesda, Maryland (Box 78)
- Harvard’s Executive Program in Public Policy and Management, 1979 (Box 78)
- Reform Issues- Oct 17, 1973 Reading Material (Box 78)
- Technical Group on Indicators Apr, 1973 (Box 78)
- C-XX Technical Group on Adjustment (Box 78)
- C-XX Material for BIS Meeting Nov, 1973 (Box 78)
- Binder- Ministerial Meeting Committee of 20 Washington DC, July 30-31, 1973 (Box 78)
- Binder-IBRD/IMF Annual Meetings Delegate Handbook Nairobi, Kenya, 9/24-28/73 (Box 78)
- C-XX Documents, March 1973-August 1973 (Box 78)
- Volcker Group Meeting, 10/10/73 (Box 78)
- First Draft Outline of Reform, Sept 1973 (Box 78)
- - Nairobi C-XX Deputies and Ministers, Sept 22-23, 1973 (Box 78)
- G-10 Meeting Sept 24, 1973 Nairobi (Box 78)
- Nairobi Misc. (Box 78)
- Briefing Material Meeting of C-20 Ministers and Deputies Sept 1973 Nairobi (Box 78)
- Nairobi Bank and Annual Meeting, Sept 24-28, 1973 (Box 79)
- Volcker Group Meeting, Sept 13, 1973 (Box 79)
- Volcker Group Meeting, Aug 27, 1973 (Box 79)
- Paris C-20 Deputies Meeting, Sept 5-7, 1973 (Box 79)
- Binder- Briefing Material Meeting of C-20 Deputies 9/5-7/73 Paris (Box 79)
- Unlabeled Binder- Tables- International Finance (Box 79)
- July30-31, 1973 Washington Meeting of Ministers of the C-20 (Box 79)
- Binder- Briefing Material Meeting of the Deputies of the C-20 DC, 11/27-29/72 (Box 79)
- Washington Meeting of C-XX Deputies, July 11-13, 1973 (Box 79)
- Binder- C-20 May 21-25, 1973 Reference Book used for Group “B” (Box 79)
- Binder- Briefing Material Meeting of C-20 Deputies, July 11-13, 1973 DC (Box 79)
- C-XX Technical Group of Global Liquidity and Consolidation, 1973 (Box 79)
- C-XX Technical Group on Intervention and Settlement (Box 79)
- Committee for Economic Development Dinner, July 24, 1973 (Box 79)
- Volcker Group Meeting, June 20, 1973 (Box 79)
- Comments on July 1973 C-20 Meeting to FOMC, July 16, 1973 (Box 79)
- Breakfast Meeting Chicago, 12/6/73 (Box 80)
- Chicago- Misc. (Box 80)
- - Chicago Speech to FRB Directors, 12/5/73 (Box 80)
- - Japanese Survey Team on Economic Policies (Irvine), 9/19/73 (Box 80)
- - Zurich Speech to American Chamber of Commerce of Switzerland, 9/11/73 (Box 80)
- - Zurich Speech to American Chamber of Commerce of Switzerland, 9/11/73 (Box 80)
- International Center Conference on Capital Movements, June 1973 (Box 80)
- Bald Peak, New Hampshire- June 27-29, 1973 FRB of Boston Conference (Box 80)
- Subcommittee on Monetary Research of the SSRC April 23, 1973 - Speech to New Directors, May 18, 1973 (Box 80)
- Interview with McKinsey and Co., April 12, 1973 (Box 80)
- Toronto- American Economic Assn. Annual Meeting, Dec 27-29, 1972 (Box 80)
- Remarks to FRS Bank and Credit Policy Group, 12/20/72 (Box 80)
- Vienna, Austrian National Bank 50th Anniversary, Nov 14, 1972 (Box 80)
- Brookings Conference-, Sept 21-22, 1972 (Box 80)
- - Washington Brookings Economic Panel, Sept 14-15, 1972 (Box 80)
- Austrian Conference, Sept 18, 1972 (Box 80)
- Madison Speech to Bank Administration Institute, July 26, 1972 (Box 80)
- - Bohemian Grove, July 20-24, 1972 (Box 80)
- Speech June 6, 1972- Directors Day (Box 80)
- - New York Discount Corporation Outing, Piping Rock Club, May 23-24, 1972 (Box 80)
- Intl. Neighbors Group Remarks, May 17, 1972 (Box 80)
- Intl. Management and Development Institute Speech, May 17, 1972 (Box 80)
- Governor Daane’s May 17, 1972 Speech (Box 80)
- - Vienna- Conf. of Officials and Academics on Intl Monetary Problems, Jan 24-27, 1973 (Box 80)
- - Remarks at Luncheon for Governor Maisel, Jan 17, 1972 (Box 80)
- - New Orleans- American Economics Assn. Annual Meeting, Dec 27-29, 1971 (Box 80)
- State Dept Survey Interview (Special Lib.), Dec 14, 1971 (Box 80)
- Investment Bankers Assn. Meeting Boca Raton Nov 30-Dec3, 1971 Invitations (Box 80)
- Conf of Federal Reserve Council, Oct 29, 1971 (Box 80)
- Study Group on the Intl Role of the Dollar Meeting, Oct 19, 1971 (Box 80)
- - Speech- Baltimore Branch Directors, Oct 14, 1971 (Box 80)
- Machlup Group and AEI Meeting (Washington), Sept 22-24, 1971 (Box 80)
- Sept 22-24, 1971- Bald Peak, NH Monetary Conf. Boston FRB (Box 80)
- Conf of Business Directors, Sept 20, 1971 (Box 80)
- Mortgage Bankers Assn Meeting with the Board, 9/9/71 (Box 80)
- Alpbach, Austria Economic Symposium, Sept 3-5, 1972 (Box 80)
- Brookings Inst.- Forum on Energy, economic Growth and the Environment, Apr 21, 1971 (Box 80)
- Boston Fed Spring Conf. Nantucket Island MA, Jun 20-22, 1971 (Box 80)
- Harvard Graduate Society Commencement Council Speech, 6/16/71 (Box 80)
- Speech to Richmond Board of Directors, Jun 10, 1971 (Box 80)
- Investment Bankers Assn Spring Meeting White Sulpher Springs, WV, May 5-8, 1971 (Box 80)
- Meeting EPC Delegation, May 5, 1971 (Box 80)
- Meeting with ABA’s Intl Banking Committee, May 3, 1971 (Box 80)
- - Meeting with Raymond Barre (V.P., Euro Comm.), Apr 30, 1971 (Box 80)
- Meeting with Canadians 6/10/70 Volcker’s Office (Box 80)
- Banker’s Assn for Foreign Trade, Apr 25-29, 2970 (Box 80)
- Cascais Meeting, 3/28-31/72 (Box 81)
- Selected Volcker Group Papers for Cascais (Box 81)
- Misc. Portugal (Box 81)
- - Speech to Securities Dealer Assn. NY, Mar 11, 1971 (Box 81)
- Conf of Business Economists, 2/11/71 (Box 81)
- Burgenstock Group Meeting - Tarrytown, NY, Feb 4-5, 1971 (Box 81)
- Joint Conf of Officials and Academics, Taormina, Sicily, Jan 22-23, 1970 (Box 81)
- Third Brookings Panel on Economic Activity 12/3-4/70 Brookings Inst. (Box 81)
- Luncheon Meeting with Committee for Economic Development, 11/23/70 DC (Box 81)
- Seminar- Task Force on Foreign Operations, 11/23/70 (Box 81)
- IMF Consultants with the US Final Session 11/19/70 Treasury (Box 81)
- Joint meeting of the Board of Reserve Bank Presidents, 11/17/70 (Box 81)
- EPC Meeting 11/12/70 EOB (Box 81)
- 46th Annual Convention of Bank Administration Inst. Washington, Nov 1-4, 1970 (Box 81)
- Georgetown Bankers Forum, Georgetown University, 10/31/70 (Box 81)
- FRB- SSRC Joint Conf. 10/30-31/70 Mayflower Hotel (Box 81)
- Associated Harvard Alumni Directors Meeting, 10/16-17/70 (Box 81)
- FRB Richmond: Young Bankers Seminar May14-15, and 21-22, 1958 (Box 81)
- Speech- Charlotte Board of Directors Mechanics of Open Market Operations, 9/18/56 (Box 81)
- Speech- The Mechanics of Open Market Operations, The Citadel, 5/2/56 (Box 81)